Alright, I'm going to play next a short video from Anna Pereira, an Active Inference Institute research fellow.
Hey, Anna Pereira here.
I was disappointed that there was an irresolvable conflict during the time of the symposium, but wanted to share or contribute a small update nonetheless.
For those of you who haven't had a chance to hear from me before,
We've been looking at accelerating and disseminating active inference for the humanities.
We're actually just starting to call it AIH.
And we continue to make progress and quietly incubate in the background.
We're not really at a point to do a large, more solid update.
But we want to quickly say hello and say that we are incubating.
We continue to be available for collaborations or conversations that others find useful.
And also to provide an update that we've been really grateful for the opportunity to incubate within the larger AI structure.
This has provided several mutualistic affordances, has been a really great construct within the larger AI
space.
So we look forward to being in touch at future conferences and symposiums and available for conversations.
In the meantime, wishing you a great symposium and be well.
Ciao.
Alright.